Labor Arbitration Opinions and Awards 5443
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Vols. 39-40: International Salt - Kim (Box 19)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 39, 1958-1964 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 39, 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 39, 1959-1964 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 39, 1959-1964 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.39, 1958-1964 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 40, 1957-1963 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. KQED Station to Kimberly-Clark Corp.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 40, 1957-1963 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 40, 1956-1964 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 40, 1957-1964 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 40, 1957-1964 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 40, 1958-1964 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Vols. 41-42: Kla - Lincoln Coach (Box 20)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 41, 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Klamath Falls Independent Grocery Employers' Committee to Lanai Plantation, Hawaiian Co., LTD.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 41, 1957-1963 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 41, 1957-1964 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 41, 1957-1962 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 41, 1960-1963 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 41, 1957-1963 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 42, 1957-1964 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Table Of Contents. Lancaster Glass Corp. to Lincoln Coach Lines.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 42, 1957-1964 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 42, 1957-1963 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 42, 1957-1964 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 42, 1957-1963 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 42, 1957-1964 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Vols. 43-44: Lincoln County to McC (Box 21)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 43, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Lincoln County Electric Membership Cooperative to Lockhead Georgia Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 43, 1957-1962 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 43, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 43, 1957-1959 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 43, 1959-1964 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 43, 1962-1964 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 44, 1961-1963 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. Lockhead Georgia Co. to McCord Corp
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 44, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 44, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 44, 1958-1963 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 44, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 44, 1957-1964 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Vols. 45-46: McDonnell Aircraft to Mason and Hanger (Box 22)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 45, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. McDonnell Aircraft Cop. To Magnetic Winding Company
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 45, 1958-1963 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 45, 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 45, 1957-1963 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 45, 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 45, 1956-1964 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 45, 1959-1963 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 46, 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Table Of Contents. Magnetic, Inc. to Mason and Hanger - Sillas Mason Co., Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 46, 1958-1964 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 46, 1957-1964 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 46, 1957-1963 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 46, 1957-1964 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 46, 1957-1964 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Vols. 47-48: Mason R - Monarch (Box 23)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 47, 1958-1964 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Mason- Rust to Merrill -Stevens Dry Stock and Repairs Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 47, 1957-1964 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 47, 1961-1964 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 47, 1958-1962 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 47, 1958-1964 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 48, 1958-1964 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Table of Contents. Merritt-Chapman and Scott Corp. to Midwest Piping Division of Crane Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 48, 1961-1964 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 48, 1954-1964 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 48, 1957-1964 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 48, 1961-1964 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Vols. 49-50: Mie - National Bea (Box 24)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 49, 1957-1964 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Miehle-Goss-Dexter, Inc. to Monarch Rubber Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 49, 1957-1964 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 49, 1957-1963 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 49, 1957-1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 49, 1960-1963 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 49, 1957-1964 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.50, 1957-1965 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. Monroe Calculating Machine Co. to Monroe Bearing Division of American Brake Shoe Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.50, 1958-1964 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.50, 1958-1964 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.50, 1952-1963 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.50, 1959-1964 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Vols. 51-52: Nat'l Biscuit - New York C (Box 25)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.51, 1957-1963 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. National Biscuit Co. to National -Standard Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.51, 1957-1963 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.51, 1959-1963 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.51, 1958-1963 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.51, 1958-1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.51, 1958-1964 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.52, 1957-1962 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. National Starch and Chemical Corp. to New York Central Railroad, Eastern Dist.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.52, 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.52, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.52, 1957-1964 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.52, 1957-1964 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.52, 1957-1964 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.52, 1961-1963 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Vols. 53-54: New York C - New York (Box 26)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.53, 1958-1964 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. NY Central Transport Co. to NY Times.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.53, 1958-1962 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.53, 1957-1963 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.53, 1958-1964 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.53, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.53, 1961-1964 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.54, 1958-1964 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. NY World-Telegram and the Sun to NYOTEX Chemical Division of Stauffer Chemical Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.54, 1958-1964 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.54, 1957-1963 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.54, 1957-1964 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.54, 1957-1964 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Vols. 55-56: OA - Peerless C (Box 27)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.55, 1956-1963 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. OAHU Sugar Co., LTD to Overhead Door Corp.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.55, 1960-1964 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.55, 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.55, 1961-1963 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.55, 1956-1964 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.55, 1961-1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.56, 1957-1964 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. Owens-Corning Fiberglass Corp. to Peerless Corp.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 56, 1959-1964 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 56, 1957-1962 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 56, 1957-1964 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 56, 1961-1963 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 56, 1957-1964 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Vols. 57-58: Peerless E - Pittsburgh Stan (Box 28)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 57, 1958-1963 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Peerless Electric Division of H.K. Porter Co., Inc. to Phillips Chemical Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 57, 1957-1963 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 57, 1957-1964 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 57, 1958-1964 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 57, 1958-1964 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 57, 1957-1964 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 57, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 58, 1957-1964 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Table of Contents. Phillips Petroleum Co. to Pittsburgh Standard Conduit Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 58, 1958-1962 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 58, 1958-1963 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 58, 1957-1964 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 58, 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 58, 1959-1964 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Vols. 59-60: Pittsburgh Steel - RKO (Box 29)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 59, 1958-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Pittsburgh Steel Co. to Printing Industry of Washington D.C., Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 59, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 59, 1961-1964 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 59, 1960-1963 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 59, 1957-1964 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 59, 1958-1964 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 59, 1960-1964 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 60, 1957-1963 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Table of Contents. Printing Industry of Washington D.C., Inc. to RKO General Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 60, 1958-1964 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 60, 1958-1961 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 60, 1961-1964 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 60, 1957-1963 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 60, 1957-1963 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 60, 1958-1964 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Vols. 61-62: Rad - Robins (Box 30)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 61, 1957-1963 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Radio Corporation of America to Reserve Mining Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 61, 1957-1964 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 61, 1957-1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 61, 1957-1964 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 61, 1958-1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 62, 1958-1963 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    Table Of Contents. Reserve Mining Co. to Robbins and Myers, Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 62, 1957-1962 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 62, 1959-1962 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 62, 1958-1964 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 62, 1957-1963 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 62, 1957-1962 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Vols. 63-64: Robins - Schn (Box 31)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 63, 1957-1964 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Robbins Tire and Rubber Co. to Safeway Stores, Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 63, 1957-1961 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 63, 1957-1963 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 63, 1957-1964 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 63, 1958-1963 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 63, 1955-1964 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 64, 1958-1964 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. Safeway Stores, Inc. to Schneider's Transfer, Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 64, 1958-1964 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 64, 1958-1964 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 64, 1957-1964 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 64, 1957-1964 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 64, 1959-1963 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Vols. 65-66: Scho - South (Box 32)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 65, 1957-1963 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Schorndorfer Co. to Sinclair Refining Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 65, 1957-1964 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 65, 1957-1964 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 65, 1957-1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 65, 1957-1964 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 65, 1957-1964 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 66, 1960-1964 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Table of Contents. Sinclair Refining Co. to Southern Illinois Builders Association
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 66, 1959-1964 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 66, 1957-1964 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 66, 1957-1963 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 66, 1956-1963 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 66, 1957-1964 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Vols. 67-68: South - Stone (Box 33)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 67, 1958-1963 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Southern Illinois Contractors' Association to Standard Forgings Corp. Includes: Newspaper Article
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 67, 1957-1963 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 67, 1957-1964 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 67, 1957-1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 67, 1959-1964 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 67, 1957-1964 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 68, 1957-1964 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Table Of Contents. Standard Gradure Corp. to Stone Container Corp.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 68, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 68, 1958-1964 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 68, 1957-1964 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 68, 1959-1964 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 68, 1957-1963 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Vols. 69-70: Stone - Trinity (Box 34)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 69, 1957-1964 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Stoner Manufacturing Co. to Tennessee Valley Authority.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 69, 1956-1963 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 69, 1957-1964 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 69, 1958-1964 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 69, 1957-1963 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 69, 1957-1964 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 69, 1958-1963 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 70, 1957-1963 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    Terminal Paper Bag Co., Inc. to Trinity Portland Cement Division.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 70, 1958-1963 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 70, 1957-1964 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 70, 1957-1963 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 70, 1959-1964 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 70, 1958-1964 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Vols. 71-72: Trinity - USI (Box 35)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.71, 1958-1964 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Trinity Portland Cement Division to Union Division Pacific Railroad Co. Table of Contents
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.71, 1957-1964 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.71, 1957-1964 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.71, 1958-1964 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.71, 1957-1963 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.71, 1957-1964 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.72, 1957-1964 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    Union Pacific Railroad Co. to U.S. Industrial Chemicals Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.72, 1957-1964 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.72, 1957-1964 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.72, 1957-1963 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.72, 1958-1964 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Vols. 73-74: U.S. Industrial - US Steel (Box 36)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.73, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    U.S. Industrial Chemicals Co. to U.S. Steel Corp.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.73, 1958-1964 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.73, 1957-1964 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.73, 1957-1958 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.73, 1958-1959 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.73, 1959-1961 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.74, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    U.S. Steel Corp.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.74, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.74, 1961-1962 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.74, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.74, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.74, 1962-1963 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Vols. 75-76: U.S. Steel - Virginia-Carolina (Box 37)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.75, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    U.S. Steel Corp. to Universal Atlas Cement. Table of Contents.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.75, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.75, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.75, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.75, 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.75, 1957-1964 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.76, 1958-1963 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Universal Atlas Cement Co. to Virginia Carolina Chemical Corp
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.76, 1958-1964 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.76, 1959-1963 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.76, 1959-1964 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.76, 1959-1964 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol.76, 1958-1964 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Vols. 77-78: Virginia M - West (Box 38)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 78, 1958-1964 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Waterman-Bic Pen Corp. to Westinghouse Electric Corp. Table of Contents.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 78, 1958-1963 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 78, 1957-1964 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 78, 1957-1963 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 78, 1959-1962 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 77, 1957-1963 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Virginia Motel Products, Inc. to Waterbury Companies, Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 77, 1957-1964 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 77, 1957-1963 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 77, 1957-1963 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 77, 1958-1963 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Vols. 79-81: Westinghouse - ZW (Box 39)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 79, 1961-1962 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Table of Contents. Westinghouse Electric Corp. to Wilkof Steel and Supply Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 79, 1958-1964 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 79, 1957-1964 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 79, 1957-1964 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 79, 1957-1963 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 79, 1960-1964 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 80, 1958-1963 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 80, 1957-1964 (Box 39, Folder 8)